{
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "Who is the best programmer?",
      "choices": ["Mansur", "Nadira", "Turgunbek", "Aktan"],
      "answer": "Mansur"
    },
    {
      "question": "Popular front-end programming language?",
      "choices": ["Java", "Python", "C++", "JavaScript"],
      "answer": "JavaScript"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is JSX??",
      "choices": ["JavaScript-XML", "Virtual-Dom", "Hook", "State"],
      "answer": "JavaScript-XML"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is React?",
      "choices": ["Framework", "useState", "Redux", "Libriary"],
      "answer": "Libriary"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is React made of?",
      "choices": ["Hooks", "HTML", "Components", "scripts"],
      "answer": "Components"
    },    {
      "question": "How can an element be added to the end of an array?",
      "choices": ["unshift", "push", "pop", "soup"],
      "answer": "push"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which firm is better?",
      "choices": ["Codify", "Google", "Meta", "Apple"],
      "answer": "Codify"
    },
    {
      "question": "a variable that cannot be redefined?",
      "choices": ["let", "var", "const", "bir"],
      "answer": "const"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the || operator used for?",
      "choices": ["or", "and", "with", "for"],
      "answer": "or"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the && operator used for?",
      "choices": ["or", "and", "with", "for"],
      "answer": "and"
    }
  ]
}